<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Nicholas Fine</title>
 <link href="http://ndfine.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://ndfine.com/"/>
 <updated>2013-01-02T22:41:43-06:00</updated>
 <id>http://ndfine.com/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Nicholas Fine</name>
   <email>nicholas.fine@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Making Blues Brothers With John Belushi and Dan Akroyd | Vanity Fair</title>
   
   <link href="http://m.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2013/01/making-of-blues-brothers-budget-for-cocaine"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2013/01/02/making-blues-brothers-with-john-belushi-and-dan-akroyd-we-had-a-budget-for-cocaine-vanity-fair-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Ned Zeman</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2013-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/01/02/making-blues-brothers-with-john-belushi-and-dan-akroyd-we-had-a-budget-for-cocaine-vanity-fair-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Then there’s Aykroyd. Yes, Belushi occasionally tries his patience. At
one point, Aykroyd smashes his wristwatch, shouting, “Do you want to end
up like this?” But he always protects and never judges. “There was a
sense that, no matter what John did, Danny wouldn’t abandon him, that he
didn’t think John was this awful person,” Carrie Fisher says. “He was
really taking care of John.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One night at three, while filming on a deserted lot in Harvey, Illinois,
Belushi disappears. He does this sometimes. On a hunch, Aykroyd follows
a grassy path until he spies a house with a light on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh, we’re shooting a film over here,” Aykroyd tells the homeowner.
“We’re looking for one of our actors.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you mean Belushi?” the man replies. “He came in here an hour ago
and raided my fridge. He’s asleep on my couch.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only Belushi could pull this off. “America’s Guest,” Aykroyd calls him.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Doing it Wrong | Atrios</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.eschatonblog.com/2012/12/youre-doing-it-wrong.html"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/30/doing-it-wrong-atrios-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Duncan Black</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/30/doing-it-wrong-atrios-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I know, or at least hope, that reading online newspaper comments is not
the best window into the soul of humanity, but it certainly is a bit
depressing sometimes. The lack of sympathy or empathy for basically
anyone is quite stunning. Everything is always the fault of victims,
basically.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Yours, Mine, but Not Ours | Jacobin</title>
   
   <link href="http://jacobinmag.com/2012/12/yours-mine-but-not-ours/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/29/yours-mine-but-not-ours-jacobin-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Corey Robin</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/29/yours-mine-but-not-ours-jacobin-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because the rhetoric of security is one of universality and neutrality
while the reality is one of conflict and division, state officials and
elites have every motivation, and justification, to suppress heterodox
and dissenting definitions of security. And so they have, as Hobbes
predicted they could and would. But because a neutral, universal
definition of security is impossible to achieve in practice, repression
for the sake of security must be necessarily selective: only certain
groups or certain kinds of dissent will be targeted. The question then
becomes: which groups, which dissent?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because government officials are themselves connected with particular
constituencies in society — often the most powerful — they will seldom
suppress challenges to security that come from the powerful; instead
they will target the powerless and the marginal, particularly if the
powerless are mobilizing to threaten the powerful. So the US government
during WWI made it illegal to urge people, like the Socialists, not to
buy war bonds — but it did allow a Wall Street adviser to counsel his
client not to make a bad investment.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An Act Of Compromise</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.newyorker.com/reporting/2012/12/24/121224fa_fact_foer?currentPage=all&mobify=0"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/28/an-act-of-compromise-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Joshua Foer</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-28T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/28/an-act-of-compromise-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We can glimpse, glance, visualize, view, look, spy, or ogle. Stare,
gawk, or gape. Peek, watch, or scrutinize. Each word suggests some
subtly different quality: looking implies volition; spying suggests
furtiveness; gawking carries an element of social judgment and a sense
of surprise. When we try to describe an act of vision, we consider a
constellation of available meanings. But if thoughts and words exist on
different planes, then expression must always be an act of compromise.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Things that make OS X tolerable, pt 1</title>
   
   <link href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/26/things-that-make-os-x-tolerable-part-one.html"/>
   
   <updated>2012-12-26T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/26/things-that-make-os-x-tolerable-part-one</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After computing almost exclusively in Linux with &lt;a href=&quot;http://xmonad.org/&quot;&gt;xmonad&lt;/a&gt; and things like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xfree86.org/4.2.0/xmodmap.1.html&quot;&gt;xmodmap&lt;/a&gt; making it easy to do things like re-map my caps lock key into something actually useful&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, shifting to a MacBook and OS X is kind of jarring.  I’m collecting together a larger list of my recommendations, but I have two initially that made it actually possible for me to resist throwing the damn thing off the roof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both are found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://pqrs.org/index.html.en&quot;&gt;pqrs.org&lt;/a&gt;.  The first
is the oddly named &lt;a href=&quot;http://pqrs.org/macosx/keyremap4macbook/pckeyboardhack.html.en&quot;&gt;PCKeyboardHack&lt;/a&gt; and its sole purpose is to change the Caps Lock key, which is apparently more involved than your standard key remapping utility.  Caps Lock as Escape is so ingrained in my muscle memory that without it I feel like I’ve lost the ability to type since I hit esc roughly a bajillion times a day in vim.  This was vital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhat less vital, but still frustrating was my desire to make the
bottom-left button on the keyboard be left control LIKE ALL THAT IS GOOD
AND HOLY because I almost never use the Fn key and that’s where control
is meant to be.  Since I was so pleased with PCKeyboardHack, I installed
their additional utility &lt;a href=&quot;http://pqrs.org/macosx/keyremap4macbook/index.html.en&quot;&gt;KeyRemap4MacBook&lt;/a&gt; which adds a panel to your System Preferences and I mapped Fn to Control L.  One important note, you need Fn to make the Function keys work (sigh) so make sure to choose an additional modifier to cause the Fn signal to be sent&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; rel=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The Escape key, in my case.&lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; rel=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Fn to Control_L (+ Option_L+Fn to Fn) is what I chose.&lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; rel=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I Would Like To Be A Nonconformist - Interview with Nick Offerman</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.believermag.com/issues/201210/?read=interview_offerman"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/nick-offerman-interview-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Nick Offerman</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/nick-offerman-interview-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Canoeing the L.A. River unironically is like doing non-union theater in Chicago. Not a lot of people are going to hear about it, but you have the beauty of performing in a Harold Pinter play and you’re just happy to have done it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>On the meaning of ‘design’</title>
   
   <link href="http://hickox.org/on-the-meaning-of-design/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/Hickox-on-design-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>David Hickox</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/Hickox-on-design-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Web development is not typically something that can be done proficiently by one person. The range of tasks requires a level of specialization. But it’s important that we consider all of these specialists as designers working towards meeting our clients’ goals on the web. And most of all, it’s important that we communicate this within our organizations and broadcast it to our clients.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A Rational Conversation - Jessica Hopper Parses the Hallowed Return of Godspeed You Black Emperor</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.thedailyswarm.com/swarm/rational-conversation-jessica-hopper/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/10/22/A-Rational-Conversation-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Eric Drucker and Jessica Hopper</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-10-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/10/22/A-Rational-Conversation-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ED: It’s been interesting to read the first reviews of the new record. This notion keeps coming up of it being important because nothing out there right now is like it. In Mark Richardson’s Pitchfork review, he wrote, ”[GY!BE] feel out of step in a very necessary way.” It is good to have a band or an artist come around every few years to make you take stock of what you’ve been listening to and why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JH: Exactly. A band like Godspeed throws everyone else into high relief. You get a better sense of the moral topography of the underground.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ED: So for you, the best-case scenario is that a young band sees the 9.3 rating, wants to learn how to get that, does research into Godspeed You! Black Emperor, and decides, “Maybe we could do that, too”?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JH: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ED: I can live with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JH: It’s kind of the best you ask for.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Amanda Palmers Accidental Experiment With Real Communism</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/culture/2012/10/amanda-palmers-kickstarter-scandal.html"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/10/02/Accidental-Experiment-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Joshua Clover</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-10-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/10/02/Accidental-Experiment-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a time-honored dodge, which might be called “the Oompa-Loompa defense.” It goes something like this: outsourcing labor to people who will work for less is fine because they are “happy” to do it. Such practices and accompanying rationales have been continually refined—think the helpline that dials a tech in Bangalore. But the fantasy of the happy worker has taken on newer and more mind-bending aspects, as has work itself. It now includes things like the unpaid microlabor of providing content for Web sites. It includes the amateur photographer who provides her images of, say, the police killing a young black man to the local news as an “iReport” for nothing but a credit and a T-shirt. Or a music lover scratching out a review on some hip site for a byline alone. Or consider the subtlest and arguably the most exemplary case: how, in wandering the byways of Facebook and Google, you are diligently rendering gratis a host of information about the preferences and habits of you and your friends—data they sell to advertisers. This, too, is unpaid labor.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Charles Pierce | Presidential Soul</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.esquire.com/blogs/politics/The_President_And_The_Blues"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/04/26/Presidential-Soul-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Charles Pierce</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-04-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/04/26/Presidential-Soul-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Much of what the world loves about America was provided by Americans who America didn’t much love for most of its history, and when the music began to batter down the mental walls we’d thrown up between black citizens and white citizens, it was a powerful covert operation that couldn’t be beaten back with police dogs, or fire hoses, or the entire legal, political, and social architecture of American apartheid. And this president knows that, and the people who are sniping at him now know it, too, and it’s driving them around the bend. Because the president knows, as we’ve all come to know, one simple truth that binds us all as Americans, even though it’s not always self-evident — that the blues is about salvage, about a carrying forward, and about recognizing the common hellhounds that stay on all of our trails.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Weld Birmingham | Bham City Hall shows leadership, Bham school board shows its...</title>
   
   <link href="http://weldbham.com/secondfront/2012/04/10/bham-city-hall-shows-leadership-bham-school-board-shows-shows-its/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/04/11/bham-city-schools-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Kyle Whitmire</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-04-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/04/11/bham-city-schools-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;During the afternoon meeting, two parents brought their children with them to the podium, and the crowd laughed when both infants immediately began clutching at the microphone. But the sad thing is that both those parents wanted to put their children — neither of which were yet of school age — in the Birmingham City Schools. They, among others, were determined make this city’s schools a good place for their kids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mohandas Gandhi said that poverty is the most subtle form of violence. Is enrolling your children in Birmingham City Schools a subtle form of child abuse?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Update to bootstrap-will_paginate</title>
   
   <link href="http://ndfine.com/2012/03/27/update-to-bootstrap-will-paginate.html"/>
   
   <updated>2012-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/03/27/update-to-bootstrap-will-paginate</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Just pushed an update to &lt;a href=&quot;https://rubygems.org/gems/bootstrap-will_paginate&quot;&gt;bootstrap-will_paginate&lt;/a&gt; that &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/yrgoldteeth/bootstrap-will_paginate/pull/5&quot;&gt;fixes&lt;/a&gt; a bug
on sending the option &lt;code&gt;:page_links =&amp;gt; false&lt;/code&gt; to a will_paginate
setup block.  Big thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jann&quot;&gt;jann@github&lt;/a&gt; for the fix!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>EDSBS | Rick Ross Wishes You A Happy Vernal Equinox</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.everydayshouldbesaturday.com/2012/3/20/2887941/rick-ross-wishes-you-a-happy-vernal-equinox"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/03/21/rick-ross-vernal-equinox-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Spencer Hall</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-03-21T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/03/21/rick-ross-vernal-equinox-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Easter morning&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hustle made&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got them eggs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They Faberge&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You got some chickens&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got that Faberge&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Stonekettle Station | Afghanistan - The Punch Line</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.stonekettle.com/2012/03/afghanistan-punch-line.html"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/03/14/afghanistan-the-punch-line-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Jim Wright</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-03-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/03/14/afghanistan-the-punch-line-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tens of thousands of supposedly civilized Americans think the senseless
slaughter of sixteen men, women, and children was a good start. Their comments
fill the halls of America and litter the airwaves and the internet and they
don’t even have the common decency to be ashamed. The murderous clamor of the
ignorant and foolish and the brutally stupid fouls our national discourse and
stains our national soul. I’ll say in complete honesty that I truly hope that
their God does indeed exist and that one day these fuckers will stand before
His righteous wrath and be judged.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>n+1- Raise the Crime Rate</title>
   
   <link href="http://nplusonemag.com/raise-the-crime-rate"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/02/03/nplusonemag.com-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Christopher Glazek</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-02-03T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/02/03/nplusonemag.com-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Crime has not fallen in the United States—it’s been shifted. Just as Wall Street connived with regulators to transfer financial risk from spendthrift banks to careless home buyers, so have federal, state, and local legislatures succeeded in rerouting criminal risk away from urban centers and concentrating it in a proliferating web of hyperhells. The statistics touting the country’s crime-reduction miracle, when juxtaposed with those documenting the quantity of rape and assault that takes place each year within the correctional system, are exposed as not merely a lie, or even a damn lie—but as the single most shameful lie in American life.  &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
