<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Nicholas Fine</title>
 <link href="http://ndfine.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://ndfine.com/"/>
 <updated>2014-02-24T16:23:56-06:00</updated>
 <id>http://ndfine.com/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Nicholas Fine</name>
   <email>nicholas.fine@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>By Any Other Name</title>
   
   <link href="http://thecodelesscode.com/case/19"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2014/02/24/by-any-other-name-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Qi</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2014-02-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2014/02/24/by-any-other-name-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The old scribe was asked why, in his official accounts, the temples and the clans were named but the many monks and priests were not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If I gave you a sheet of figures to tally, would you first bestow a name upon each number seven?” asked the scribe, dismissing the questioner with a wave of an ink-stained hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was mentioned to the Java master, who nodded and finished his tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning the scribe ascended to his office, only to find the following written in thick block letters above the door:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static final int NUM_DAYS_IN_WEEK =&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this, the old scribe Qi was enlightened.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Using sequel-rails With A Forking Webserver</title>
   
   <link href="http://ndfine.com/2014/02/07/using-sequel-rails-with-a-forking-webserver.html"/>
   
   <updated>2014-02-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2014/02/07/using-sequel-rails-with-a-forking-webserver</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I was contracted recently for a rush job on a dashboard-style reporting
webapp using a postgres database whose schema I did not design or
control.  I had long intended on looking into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jeremyevans/sequel&quot;&gt;Sequel&lt;/a&gt; 
library for database interactions, and as I was going to be developing
the application in Rails, I was happy to see that there was also an
existing &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/TalentBox/sequel-rails&quot;&gt;sequel-rails&lt;/a&gt; gem that works almost exactly as
expected similar to the stock ActiveRecord style of Rails apps.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was able to easily make changes to the database in a migration style,
and the application in general just went off without a hitch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application needed a staging/demo server that could be provisioned
quickly, so I went with Heroku in a manner similar to the instructions
in this &lt;a href=&quot;https://devcenter.heroku.com/articles/rails-unicorn&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;, which calls for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://unicorn.bogomips.org/&quot;&gt;Unicorn&lt;/a&gt;
webserver with a configuration like so:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;text language-text&quot; data-lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;# config/unicorn.rb
worker_processes Integer(ENV[&amp;quot;WEB_CONCURRENCY&amp;quot;] || 3)
timeout 15
preload_app true

before_fork do |server, worker|
  Signal.trap &amp;#39;TERM&amp;#39; do
    puts &amp;#39;Unicorn master intercepting TERM and sending myself QUIT instead&amp;#39;
    Process.kill &amp;#39;QUIT&amp;#39;, Process.pid
  end

  defined?(ActiveRecord::Base) and
    ActiveRecord::Base.connection.disconnect!
end

after_fork do |server, worker|
  Signal.trap &amp;#39;TERM&amp;#39; do
    puts &amp;#39;Unicorn worker intercepting TERM and doing nothing. Wait for master to send QUIT&amp;#39;
  end

  defined?(ActiveRecord::Base) and
    ActiveRecord::Base.establish_connection
end
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the application does not use ActiveRecord, I removed those lines and
gave the deploy a shot, knowing it would likely become a problem.  Soon, 
it was manifesting itself by throwing 500 errors when a user logged in,
but would clear up on a refresh.  This irritated me, though, but
everything I found on the internet about using &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jeremyevans/sequel&quot;&gt;Sequel&lt;/a&gt; with a
forking webserver referred to reconnecting just using the DB object that
was always just created globally in the application, which is not how
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/TalentBox/sequel-rails&quot;&gt;sequel-rails&lt;/a&gt; does things.  So, after digging through the
code for a while I found that the DB object when using sequel-rails is
at &lt;code&gt;Sequel::Model.db&lt;/code&gt;, which allowed me to clear up the 500 errors by
making this adjustment to the config file: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;text language-text&quot; data-lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;# config/unicorn.rb
worker_processes Integer(ENV[&amp;quot;WEB_CONCURRENCY&amp;quot;] || 3)
timeout 15
preload_app true

before_fork do |server, worker|
  Signal.trap &amp;#39;TERM&amp;#39; do
    puts &amp;#39;Unicorn master intercepting TERM and sending myself QUIT instead&amp;#39;
    Process.kill &amp;#39;QUIT&amp;#39;, Process.pid
  end

  defined?(Sequel::Model) and
    Sequel::Model.db.disconnect
end

after_fork do |server, worker|
  Signal.trap &amp;#39;TERM&amp;#39; do
    puts &amp;#39;Unicorn worker intercepting TERM and doing nothing. Wait for master to send QUIT&amp;#39;
  end

  defined?(Sequel::Model) and
    Sequel::Model.db.connect(SequelRails.configuration.environment_for(Rails.env))
end
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that this saves some headaches for developers down the line.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Inferno of Independence</title>
   
   <link href="http://frankchimero.com/blog/2013/09/the-inferno-of-independence/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2013/09/24/the-inferno-of-independence-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Frank Chimero</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2013-09-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/09/24/the-inferno-of-independence-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A mythology of speed is one of willful ignorance to the small details
that hold the whole arrangement together. And, I think, if you’re
building things for the internet, those small details matter, because
they are repeated ten-fold, hundred-fold, million-fold, as they are
replicated effortlessly through screens, across the globe, and into
people’s consciousness for countless hours of exposure. Economies of
scale make small decisions matter, but speed— both in making those small
decisions and in interacting them—makes both sides blind to what’s going
on. We’re thoughtlessly writing things we can’t read, because we’re
going too fast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has any one ever considered the creepiness of social media’s interface
copy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“View friendship.”&lt;br&gt;
“Remember me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It feels perverse, awkward and foreign, yet familiar, like the best
details in a dystopian story. It’s appealing in that way, but it also
irritates me, because I love words. Words mold brains, and if you don’t
believe it, you should look at what sort of language we use about the
internet and the products (digital and not) that connect to it and are
part of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Revolutionary, disruptive, magical, wizards, and on and on—contemporary
digital culture has co-opted the language of revolution and magic
without the muscle, ethics, conviction, or imagination of either. And
it’s not that those things aren’t possible, we just aren’t living up to
their meaning and instead saturating ourselves with hyperbole. These are
words you have to earn, and slinging them around strips the words of
their powerful meaning. Can you take a real revolution seriously if you
are bombarded with messaging that your phone is revolutionary?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Quick Note Regarding Terminal Clearing and vi Mode</title>
   
   <link href="http://ndfine.com/2013/08/05/quick-note-regarding-terminal-clearning-and-vi-mode.html"/>
   
   <updated>2013-08-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/08/05/quick-note-regarding-terminal-clearning-and-vi-mode</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have switched from using emacs keybindings in my terminal emulator
into using vi (&lt;code&gt;set -o vi&lt;/code&gt;), which feels pure and holy.  The only problem is I was
missing the screen clearing that &lt;code&gt;Control-L&lt;/code&gt; affords.  Fix this by
creating a &lt;code&gt;.inputrc&lt;/code&gt; file in your home directory with the following
line (or appending it to your existing &lt;code&gt;.inputrc&lt;/code&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;text language-text&quot; data-lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;bind -m vi-insert &amp;quot;\C-l&amp;quot;:clear-screen
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Doubling Down</title>
   
   <link href="http://davidsimon.com/doubling-down/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2013/07/17/doubling-down-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>David Simon</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2013-07-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/07/17/doubling-down-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Why not? Because just as good cannot be truly understood to the marrow
without a corresponding sense of evil, pride in one’s country — if it is
substantive pride, and not merely the rote, pledge-allegiance mouthings
of patriotic cliche — requires the sober knowledge that American
greatness is neither assured, nor heaven-sent. It comes to us from our
national premise and ideals — and our willingness to maintain those
things at all hazards. And if you’ve never felt ashamed for us for
having strayed from our core values in even the most appalling ways —
say, the wartime detention of Japanese-Americans, or a My Lai or Kent
State , or Bull Conner, or COINTELPRO, or life sentences for juvenile
defendants, or prisons-for-profit — then maybe you’ve never really
acknowledged what the actual stakes are for a republic, or how much
work, rather than platitude, is required to assure an honorable,
democratic future. Yes, you claim an all-encompassing pride and you
wallow in it, brooking not even a mention of anything shameful that
happens on our watch as citizens. But in fact, real pride is earned and
internalized only with a grown-up understanding that even a good or
great nation, while deserving of our allegiance and civic commitment,
can indeed shame itself. Saying so when it happens is a fundamental of
self-governance, as all dissent is a fundamental of self-governance.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Paris Bureau -- Dispatch</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/07/the-paris-bureau-dispatch-1/277559/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2013/07/06/the-paris-bureau-dispatch-1-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Ta-Nehisi Coates</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2013-07-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/07/06/the-paris-bureau-dispatch-1-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;But the game is rigged. I know this because I loved my craft for many
years and it meant nothing to anyone save my mother, my father, my
siblings, my wife and a few close friends. Then one man of some
privilege spoke to another man of some privilege and I became a man of
some privilege with megaphone, which I now employ, across an ocean, to
bring these thoughts to you. And I love both of these men of
privilege--power is a fact, it is not morality. Losing is tragic, but it
is not noble. How many freedom fighters turned despots in the possession
of superior guns?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Alice's Restaurant, Gritty Thriller Edition</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.joshmillard.com/2012/11/22/alices-restaurant-gritty-thriller-edition/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2013/04/26/alice-s-restaurant-gritty-thriller-edition-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Josh Millard</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2013-04-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/04/26/alice-s-restaurant-gritty-thriller-edition-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;ARLO sitting in a holding cell. BIG UGLY approaches, heavy danger vibes,
this is a bad scene. He stares right down at ARLO, pops knuckles, and
says: “what are you in for?” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arlo stares right back at him, all intensity. Cut over to super-fast
montage of ARLO fighting a guy, ARLO killing the guy, ARLO chucking the
guy over a cliff, body falling among a pile of trash. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cut back to ARLO staring up at BIG UGLY. Deadpan response: “littering”.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Crimes against history are crimes against humanity | Digby</title>
   
   <link href="http://digbysblog.blogspot.com/2013/01/crimes-against-history-are-crimes.html"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2013/01/29/crimes-against-history-are-crimes-against-humanity-digby-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>David Atkins</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2013-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/01/29/crimes-against-history-are-crimes-against-humanity-digby-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;There are those who will mock me for caring more about dusty old books
and statues than about real people. Fine. But generations come and go.
People live, die and are largely forgotten. History is forever. All of
humanity is the same species, and our species has survived literally
countless wars, ethnic cleansings, incursions and imperial aggressions.
But once an irreplaceable artifact of history is gone, it&amp;#39;s gone
forever. Thanks largely to a similarly barbaric cleansing on history on
the part of early Christians, the world has lost 107 of Livy&amp;#39;s 142 books
of Roman history, as well as Aristotle&amp;#39;s &lt;em&gt;On Comedy&lt;/em&gt;--both losses of
enormous consequence. These are crucial pieces of the human experience
we will never recover.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Making Blues Brothers With John Belushi and Dan Akroyd | Vanity Fair</title>
   
   <link href="http://m.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2013/01/making-of-blues-brothers-budget-for-cocaine"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2013/01/02/making-blues-brothers-with-john-belushi-and-dan-akroyd-we-had-a-budget-for-cocaine-vanity-fair-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Ned Zeman</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2013-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2013/01/02/making-blues-brothers-with-john-belushi-and-dan-akroyd-we-had-a-budget-for-cocaine-vanity-fair-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Then there’s Aykroyd. Yes, Belushi occasionally tries his patience. At
one point, Aykroyd smashes his wristwatch, shouting, “Do you want to end
up like this?” But he always protects and never judges. “There was a
sense that, no matter what John did, Danny wouldn’t abandon him, that he
didn’t think John was this awful person,” Carrie Fisher says. “He was
really taking care of John.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One night at three, while filming on a deserted lot in Harvey, Illinois,
Belushi disappears. He does this sometimes. On a hunch, Aykroyd follows
a grassy path until he spies a house with a light on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh, we’re shooting a film over here,” Aykroyd tells the homeowner.
“We’re looking for one of our actors.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, you mean Belushi?” the man replies. “He came in here an hour ago
and raided my fridge. He’s asleep on my couch.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only Belushi could pull this off. “America’s Guest,” Aykroyd calls him.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Doing it Wrong | Atrios</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.eschatonblog.com/2012/12/youre-doing-it-wrong.html"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/30/doing-it-wrong-atrios-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Duncan Black</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/30/doing-it-wrong-atrios-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I know, or at least hope, that reading online newspaper comments is not
the best window into the soul of humanity, but it certainly is a bit
depressing sometimes. The lack of sympathy or empathy for basically
anyone is quite stunning. Everything is always the fault of victims,
basically.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Yours, Mine, but Not Ours | Jacobin</title>
   
   <link href="http://jacobinmag.com/2012/12/yours-mine-but-not-ours/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/29/yours-mine-but-not-ours-jacobin-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Corey Robin</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/29/yours-mine-but-not-ours-jacobin-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because the rhetoric of security is one of universality and neutrality
while the reality is one of conflict and division, state officials and
elites have every motivation, and justification, to suppress heterodox
and dissenting definitions of security. And so they have, as Hobbes
predicted they could and would. But because a neutral, universal
definition of security is impossible to achieve in practice, repression
for the sake of security must be necessarily selective: only certain
groups or certain kinds of dissent will be targeted. The question then
becomes: which groups, which dissent?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because government officials are themselves connected with particular
constituencies in society — often the most powerful — they will seldom
suppress challenges to security that come from the powerful; instead
they will target the powerless and the marginal, particularly if the
powerless are mobilizing to threaten the powerful. So the US government
during WWI made it illegal to urge people, like the Socialists, not to
buy war bonds — but it did allow a Wall Street adviser to counsel his
client not to make a bad investment.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An Act Of Compromise</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.newyorker.com/reporting/2012/12/24/121224fa_fact_foer?currentPage=all&mobify=0"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/28/an-act-of-compromise-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Joshua Foer</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-28T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/28/an-act-of-compromise-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We can glimpse, glance, visualize, view, look, spy, or ogle. Stare,
gawk, or gape. Peek, watch, or scrutinize. Each word suggests some
subtly different quality: looking implies volition; spying suggests
furtiveness; gawking carries an element of social judgment and a sense
of surprise. When we try to describe an act of vision, we consider a
constellation of available meanings. But if thoughts and words exist on
different planes, then expression must always be an act of compromise.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Things that make OS X tolerable, pt 1</title>
   
   <link href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/26/things-that-make-os-x-tolerable-part-one.html"/>
   
   <updated>2012-12-26T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/26/things-that-make-os-x-tolerable-part-one</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After computing almost exclusively in Linux with &lt;a href=&quot;http://xmonad.org/&quot;&gt;xmonad&lt;/a&gt; and things like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xfree86.org/4.2.0/xmodmap.1.html&quot;&gt;xmodmap&lt;/a&gt; making it easy to do things like re-map my caps lock key into something actually useful[^1], shifting to a MacBook and OS X is kind of jarring.  I&amp;#39;m collecting together a larger list of my recommendations, but I have two initially that made it actually possible for me to resist throwing the damn thing off the roof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both are found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://pqrs.org/index.html.en&quot;&gt;pqrs.org&lt;/a&gt;.  The first
is the oddly named &lt;a href=&quot;http://pqrs.org/macosx/keyremap4macbook/pckeyboardhack.html.en&quot;&gt;PCKeyboardHack&lt;/a&gt; and its sole purpose is to change the Caps Lock key, which is apparently more involved than your standard key remapping utility.  Caps Lock as Escape is so ingrained in my muscle memory that without it I feel like I&amp;#39;ve lost the ability to type since I hit esc roughly a bajillion times a day in vim.  This was vital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhat less vital, but still frustrating was my desire to make the
bottom-left button on the keyboard be left control LIKE ALL THAT IS GOOD
AND HOLY because I almost never use the Fn key and that&amp;#39;s where control
is meant to be.  Since I was so pleased with PCKeyboardHack, I installed
their additional utility &lt;a href=&quot;http://pqrs.org/macosx/keyremap4macbook/index.html.en&quot;&gt;KeyRemap4MacBook&lt;/a&gt; which adds a panel to your System Preferences and I mapped Fn to Control L.  One important note, you need Fn to make the Function keys work (sigh) so make sure to choose an additional modifier to cause the Fn signal to be sent[^2].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[^1]: The Escape key, in my case.
[^2]: Fn to Control&lt;em&gt;L (+ Option&lt;/em&gt;L+Fn to Fn) is what I chose.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I Would Like To Be A Nonconformist - Interview with Nick Offerman</title>
   
   <link href="http://www.believermag.com/issues/201210/?read=interview_offerman"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/nick-offerman-interview-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>Nick Offerman</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/nick-offerman-interview-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Canoeing the L.A. River unironically is like doing non-union theater in Chicago. Not a lot of people are going to hear about it, but you have the beauty of performing in a Harold Pinter play and you’re just happy to have done it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>On the meaning of ‘design’</title>
   
   <link href="http://hickox.org/on-the-meaning-of-design/"/>
   <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/Hickox-on-design-from-pinboard.html"/>
   <author>
     <name>David Hickox</name>
   </author>
   
   <updated>2012-12-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://ndfine.com/2012/12/13/Hickox-on-design-from-pinboard</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Web development is not typically something that can be done proficiently by one person. The range of tasks requires a level of specialization. But it’s important that we consider all of these specialists as designers working towards meeting our clients’ goals on the web. And most of all, it’s important that we communicate this within our organizations and broadcast it to our clients.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
